Escape is just the beginning.
Bound to Vengeance is a thriller, horror film directed by José Manuel Cravioto.
A young woman, Eve, fights back and manages to escape a malicious abductor.
However, after discovering she may not be the only victim, Eve unravels a
darker truth and decides to turn the tables on her captor.
Eve Pritchard, played by Tina Ivlev.
Phil, played by Richard Tyson.
Lea, played by Bianca Malinowski.
Ronnie Taylor, played by Kris Kjornes.
Laura, played by Dustin Quick.
Nina, played by Stephanie Charles.
Bound to Vengeance is a 2015 American horror-thriller film about a woman who
escapes her confinement in a basement by a sexual predator.
The film had its world premiere on January 23,
2015 at the Sundance Film Festival.
The film explores themes of van, escape, kidnapping, revenge, murder.
The tone is dark and intense.